humansarefree.com 2019-11-26

# PRIVACY POLICY | Humans Are Free

Privacy Policy We take your privacy seriously. This policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. (This privacy p...

Privacy Policy  
  
We take your privacy seriously. This policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. (This privacy policy is applicable to websites falling under the primary holder Humans Are Free, http://www.HumansAreFree.com.)  
  
Routine Information Collection  
  
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets me know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors.  
  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
  
Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.  
  
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.  
  
Controlling Your Privacy  
  
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.  
  
Special Note About Google Advertising  
  
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies.  
  
About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Affiliate advertising**

Our website contains affiliate marketing links, which means we may get paid commission on sales of those products or services we write about. If you take action (i.e. subscribe, make a purchase, etc.) after clicking one of these links, we’ll earn some coffee money, which we promise to drink while creating more content for you to read. 

Unless stated otherwise, our editorial content is not influenced by advertisers or affiliate partnerships. This disclosure is provided in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission's 16 CFR § 255.5: [Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising](http://www.ftc.gov/sites/default/files/attachments/press-releases/ftc-publishes-final-guides-governing-endorsements-testimonials/091005revisedendorsementguides.pdf).  
  
Medical disclaimer

This website is not intended for the purpose of providing medical advice. The views of the authors are not necessarily shared by http://HumansAreFree.com.    
  
The information found here is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis or treatment and is for information only. Always seek the advice of your physician or another qualified health provider with any questions about your medical condition and/or current medication. 

All information, content, and material of this website is for informational purposes only and are not intended to serve as a substitute for the consultation, diagnosis, and/or medical treatment of a qualified physician or healthcare provider.  Do not disregard professional medical advice or delay seeking advice or treatment because of something you have read here.  
  
Contact Information  
  
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to alexandru2012@gmail.com for further clarification.
